# Vijay Goswami

Agra, Uttar Pradesh, India



hexpit@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/hexpit



9045533427



https://vijaygoswami.in

# Summary

I am a passionate Full Stack Web Developer having experience in developing more than 150 commercial applications so far. I have expertise with building ERP web applications and I advocate using TALL STACK (abbr for TailwindCSS, AlpineJS, Laravel, Livewire) for frontend development.

I love to work with different development environments and have quite good experience with macOS, Linux (Debian/CentOS) and Windows. I am a big fan of the Apple Eco-system and it is my preferred development setup. I love to contribute to the OSS community and I am a proud contributor to a number of Open Source Projects (kindly see my GitHub profile for updated projects list).

## **Experience**



#### Guest Lecturer

Dr. B. R. Ambedkar University, Agra

2015 - Dec 2020 (6 years)

I worked as a guest lecturer in Dr. B. R. Ambedkar University (Formarly - Agra University). My role in the organization was to teach web development to ADIT (Advance Diploma in Information Technology).



### Founder Founder

Attrix Technologies Apr 2010 - Present (11 years 11 months +) Trainer/ Developer

#### **Education**



# Hindustan College of Science & Technology

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Science 2005 - 2010

### **Licenses & Certifications**



Microsoft Certified Systems Engineer: Windows Server 2003 (MCSE)

#### Skills

Laravel • PHP • JavaScript • Web Application Development • API Development • ERP Software • Software as a Service (SaaS) • Livewire • Alpine • Tailwind CSS